A Guide to the Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia, Dockets, 1965-1987
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
The Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia, Dockets 1965-1987
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-1/1/7.911
This collection consists of 21 boxes.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was an archival transfer, 1991 August 26.
Scope and Content Information
The collection consists of dockets for regular and called meetings of the Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia.
Contents List
- Dockets 1965 Feb 6 (Box 1)
- Dockets 1965 Apr 9 (Box 1)
- Dockets--Called Meeting 1965 Apr 9 (Box 1)
- Dockets--Board Meeting 1965 Jun 4 (Box 1)
- Dockets 1965 Jun 4 (Box 1)
- Dockets--Called Meeting 1965 Jun 24 (Box 1)
- Dockets 1965 Oct 8 (Box 2)
- Dockets 1965 Dec 11 (Box 2)
- Dockets--Called Meeting 1966 Jan 8 (Box 2)
- Dockets 1966 Feb 12 (Box 2)
- Dockets--Called Meeting 1966 Feb 26 (Box 2)
- Dockets 1966 Apr 2 (Box 2)
- Dockets--Board Minutes and Committee Minutes 1966 Jun 3 (Box 2)
- Dockets 1966 Jun 3 (Box 3)
- Dockets 1966 Oct 7 (Box 3)
- Dockets 1966 Dec 10 (Box 3)
- Dockets--Meeting Folder 1967 Feb 18 (Box 3)
- Dockets--Meeting Folder 1967 Apr 8 (Box 3)
- Dockets--Meeting Folder 1967 Jun 2 (Box 4)
- Dockets--Meeting Folder 1967 Oct 13 (Box 4)
- Dockets--Meeting Folder 1967 Dec 9 (Box 4)
- Dockets--Meeting Folder 1968 Feb 17 (Box 4)
- Dockets--Meeting Folder 1968 Apr 19 (Box 4)
- Dockets--Meeting Folder 1968 Jun 7 (Box 4)
- Dockets--Meeting Folder 1968 Oct 4 (Box 5)
- Dockets--Meeting Folder 1968 Dec 14 (Box 5)
- Dockets 1969 Apr 5 (Box 5)
- Dockets 1969 Feb 15 (Box 5)
- Dockets 1969 Jun 6 (Box 5)
- Dockets 1969 Oct 3 (Box 5)
- Dockets 1969 Dec 6 (Box 6)
- Dockets 1970 Feb 7 (Box 6)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1970 Mar 9 (Box 6)
- Dockets--Meeting Folder 1970 Apr 11 (Box 6)
- Dockets--Board Meeting 1970 Jun 5 (Box 6)
- Dockets--Board Meeting 1970 Oct 2 (Box 6)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1970 Dec 4 (Box 7)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1971 Feb 13 (Box 7)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1971 Apr 3 (Box 7)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1971 Jun 4 (Box 7)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1971 Oct 1 (Box 7)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1971 Dec 11 (Box 7)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1972 Feb 3 (Box 8)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1972 Apr 7 (Box 8)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1972 Jun 2 (Box 8)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1972 Oct 13 (Box 8)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1972 Dec 8 (Box 8)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1973 Feb 2 (Box 8)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1973 Apr 6 (Box 9)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1973 Jun 1 (Box 9)
- Dockets--Special Meeting 1973 Sep 14 (Box 9)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1973 Oct 26 (Box 9)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1974 Jan 24 (Box 9)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1974 Mar 29 (Box 9)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1974 May 17 (Box 10)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1974 Oct 11 (Box 10)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1975 Jan 10 (Box 10)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1975 Mar 14 (Box 10)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1975 May 30 (Box 10)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1975 Oct 3 (Box 10)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1976 Jan 23 (Box 11)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1976 Mar 26 (Box 11)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1976 May 28 (Box 11)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1976 Oct 14 (Box 11)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1977 Jan 22 (Box 11)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1977 Apr 2 (Box 12)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1977 Oct 8 (Box 12)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1977 Jun 4 (Box 12)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1978 Jan 28 (Box 12)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1978 Apr 1 (Box 12)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1978 Jun 2 (Box 12)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1978 Oct 7 (Box 13)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1979 Jan 27 (Box 13)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1979 Mar 31 (Box 13)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1979 Jun 2 (Box 13)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1979 Oct 6 (Box 13)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1980 Jan 26 (Box 14)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1980 Mar 22 (Box 14)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1980 Jun 7 (Box 14)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1980 Oct 4 (Box 14)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1981 Jan 31 (Box 15)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1981 Mar 27 (Box 15)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1981 Jun 5 (Box 15)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1981 Oct 10 (Box 15)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1982 Jan 30 (Box 16)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1982 Mar 26 (Box 16)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1982 Jun 5 (Box 16)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1982 Oct 16 (Box 17)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1983 Jan 22 (Box 17)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1983 Mar 26 (Box 17)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1983 Jun 3 (Box 17)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1983 Oct 8 (Box 17)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1984 Jan 27 (Box 17)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1984 Mar 30 (Box 18)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1984 Jun 1 (Box 18)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1984 Oct 5 (Box 18)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1985 Jan 25 (Box 18)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1985 Mar 29 (Box 19)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1985 May 31 (Box 19)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1985 Oct 11 (Box 19)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1985 Oct 11 (Box 19)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1986 Jan 31 (Box 19)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1986 Jan 31 (Box 20)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1986 Mar 21 (Box 20)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1986 Mar 21 (Box 20)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1986 May 30 (Box 20)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1986 Oct 3 (Box 20)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1986 Oct 3 (Box 20)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1987 Jan 30 (Box 21)
- Dockets--Regular Meeting 1987 Jan 30 (Box 21)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1987 Mar 27 (Box 21)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1987 May 29 (Box 21)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1987 Oct 2 (Box 21)
- Dockets--Regular Board Meeting 1987 Oct 2 (Box 21)